

# **Angelique Schouten**

Zaagmolenkade 221
3035 KD Rotterdam
mail@angeliqueschouten.com
https://www.angeliqueschouten.com
https://github.com/Ange1ique
+31 (0)6 421 06 334

## **Ambition**

Since two years I have been focused on software development with a lot of enthusiasm and motivation. Looking back on all my experiences I realized that a lot of my skills and assets are of value for this discipline: my love for puzzles, my creativity, perseverance, accuracy and my analytical problem solving skills. I get energy from fixing bugs, I am good in turning ideas into action and I learn new methods and software easily. This is why it is my goal to become an expert in software development and with that to add value to society.

### **Characteristics**

technical | creative | driven precise | loyal | customer oriented

### **Hobbies**

programming | climbing | puzzle hiking | being creative

# Project experience in IT

PWA WITH MULTI-TENANT SAAS ARCHITECTURE - Client: Edition1

- Teamwork
- Python | Django | PostgreSQL | React | Docker | Traefik | Postman

MULTILINGUAL MULTI-SITE - Client: Be Event

- Individual work and responsibility (excl. setting up test and prod env)
- Back-end 40% added multilingual and multi-site functionality, developed search module and function for automatically deleting 2 month old data
- Front-end 100% according to design in PDF
- Python | Django | Wagtail | PostgreSQL | Elasticsearch | Docker

WEB APP - Client: imaginary hair dresser with multiple locations

- In scrum team during DevOps bootcamp
- App with accounts, multiple roles, a webshop and appointments module
- Python | Flask | SQLAlchemy | Gherkin | Behave | Selenium

Also see my portfolio website: www.angeliqueschouten.com

### **Education**

#### IT-CERTIFICATES 2019 / 2020

- OpenCert Automated Application Testing
- OpenCert DevOps Fundamentals
- IREB Certified Professional for Requirements Engineering FL
- ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level
- Scrum.org Professional Scrum Master (PSM1)
- HarvardX CS50's Introduction to Computer Science
- Udemy Python and Django Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp
- MITx Introduction to Computer Science and Programming Using Python

#### BOOTCAMP DEVOPS ENGINEER THROUGH YOUNGCAPITAL NEXT

Testconsultancy Groep, ITPH Academy, Zwolle, January 2020 - March 2020

#### MSc INTEGRATED PRODUCT DESIGN

TU Delft, January 2004 - September 2006 Graduation project was graded with a 9

#### **BSc INDUSTRIAL DESIGN**

TU Delft, September 1999 - January 2005

## Work experience

#### JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Edition1, Den Haaq, May 2020 - present

See project experience at top of page (for Be Event and Edition1)

#### **OWN COMPANY**

Lampshapers, Rotterdam, October 2014 - January 2020

- 3d CAD modelling of the lighting designs
- Developing and maintaining the international web shop in WordPress
- Switch to open source software and other CAD software